<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Yi Mei @ VUW</title>
    <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Yi Mei @ VUW</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/hero_carousel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/hero_carousel/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/slider/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/slider/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academic</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/hero/</guid>
      <description>The highly flexible website framework for Hugo with an extensible plugin mechanism. Create a beautifully simple site in under 10 minutes 🚀 Latest release   Star</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/news/</guid>
      <description>[PhD Vacancy] I am looking for PhD/MSc/Honours/Summer Research students in Evolutionary Computation and Machine Learning for Scheduling and Combinatorial Optimisation. If you have similar research interests with me, please do not hesitate to contact me.
 [Call for papers] We are organising IEEE Symposium on Evolutionary scheduling and combinatorial optimisation (IEEE ESCO). Submission due date: August 1, 2019.
 2018-12, our paper won the Australasian Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence Best Paper Runner-Up Award!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/skills/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/experience/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Accomplish&amp;shy;ments</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/accomplishments/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/accomplishments/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/research/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grants &amp; Awards</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/grants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/grants/</guid>
      <description>Grants  2020-2027, &amp;ldquo;A data-science driven evolution of aquaculture for building the blue economy (AI/ML Advanced Research and Applications to Aquaculture)&amp;rdquo;. MBIE SSIF Fund on Data Science, $13,000,000 NZD. (Key Researcher) 2019-2020, &amp;ldquo;AI/ML techniques for Waste Collection in NZ&amp;rdquo;, industrial project with Northland Waste, $16,000 NZD. (PI) 2017-2020, &amp;ldquo;Automatic Design of Heuristics for Dynamic Arc Routing Problem with Genetic Programming&amp;rdquo;, 16-VUW-079, Marsden Fund Fast-Start Grant, $300,000 NZD. (Sole PI) 2017-2020, &amp;ldquo;Cooperative Co-evolution for Large Scale Black Box Optimisation&amp;rdquo;, 61673194, National Natural Science Foundation of China, &amp;yen;610,000 RMB (Overseas AI)  2018, &amp;ldquo;Real-Time Tourist Trip Recommendation using Genetic Programming&amp;rdquo;, University Research Fund, Victoria University of Wellington, $28,720 NZD (Sole PI) 2016-2018, &amp;ldquo;Digital Data in Schools: An Exploration of Research and Practice&amp;rdquo;, Victoria University of Wellington Digital Future Grant, $20,000 NZD (Co-PI) 2017, &amp;ldquo;Evolving Interpretable Flexible Job Shop Scheduling Rules with GP&amp;rdquo;, Research Establishment Grant, Victoria University of Wellington, $10,000 NZD (Sole PI) 2014, RMIT Near-miss grant ($25,000 AUD awarded for being ranked top 10% of the unsuccessful applications for the 2014 ARC DECRA funding) 2009, IEEE CIS Walter Karplus Summer Research Grant  Awards  2018, Victoria University of Wellington Early Research Excellence Award 2018, Australasian Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence Best Paper Runner-Up Award (paper) 2018, International Conference on Web Services (ARC/CORE Rank A) Best Paper Runner-Up (paper) 2017, IEEE Transactions on Evolutionary Computation (top journal in EC, IF = 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Featured Publications</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/publications_featured/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/publications_featured/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Publications</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/publications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Featured Talks</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/talks_featured/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/talks_featured/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/talks/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/teaching/</guid>
      <description> 2020  Algorithms and Data Structures (COMP261) [Course Coordinator] Introduction to Artificial Intelligence (COMP307) Artificial Intelligence (COMP420) Data Mining, Neural Networks and Genetic Programming (COMP422) [Course Coordinator]  2019  Algorithms and Data Structures (COMP261) [Course Coordinator] Introduction to Artificial Intelligence (COMP307) Data Mining, Neural Networks and Genetic Programming (COMP422) [Acting Course Coordinator]  2018  Algorithms and Data Structures (COMP261) [Course Coordinator] Design and Analysis of Algorithms (COMP361) [Course Coordinator] Introduction to Artificial Intelligence (COMP307) Data Mining, Neural Networks and Genetic Programming (COMP422)  2017  Algorithms and Data Structures (COMP261) Software Development (SWEN221) Data Mining, Neural Networks and Genetic Programming (COMP422) Database System Engineering (SWEN304)  2016  Introduction to Artificial Intelligence (COMP307) Data Mining, Neural Network and Genetic Programming (COMP422)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supervision</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/supervision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/supervision/</guid>
      <description>I am a supervisor of 17 PhD students and 7 Master students, as well as a number of honours and summer research students (full list).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Services</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/services/</guid>
      <description>Editorship  Associate Editor of International Journal of Applied Evolutionary Computation Editorial Board Member of International Journal of Bio-Inspired Computation Editorial Board Member of International Journal of Automation and Control Guest Editor of Special Issue on Automated Design and Adaptation of Heuristics for Scheduling and Combinatorial Optimisation, Genetic Programming and Evolvable Machines, 2016  Conference Organisation  Proceedings Chair, IEEE Congress on Evolutionary Computation (CEC) 2019 Tutorial Co-chair, Pacific Rim International Conferences on Artificial Intelligence (PRICAI) 2019 Sponsorship Chair, Australasian Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence 2018 Technical Co-chair, International Conference on Data Intelligence and Security (ICDIS) 2018 Organisational Committee Member, International Conference on Computers and Industrial Engineering (CIE) 2018 Co-Chair, IEEE Symposium on Evolutionary Scheduling and Combinatorial Optimisation, in IEEE SSCI 2019, 2020 Co-chair of Special Session on Evolutionary Scheduling and Combinatorial Optimisation, IEEE Congress on Evolutionary Computation (CEC) 2016, 2017, 2018, 2019, 2020 Co-chair of Special Session on Evolutionary Computation for Service-Oriented Computing, IEEE Congress on Evolutionary Computation (CEC) 2017, 2018, 2019 Co-chair of Special Session on Transfer Learning in Evolutionary Computation, IEEE Congress on Evolutionary Computation (CEC) 2016 Co-chair of Special Session on Computational Intelligence for Scheduling and Combinatorial Optimization, Asia-Pacific Symposium on Intelligent and Evolutionary Systems (IES) 2016  Conference Program Committee Member I serve as a PC member of ~40 international conferences (full list).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Posts</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/posts/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/resources/</guid>
      <description>Useful Resources Code  My Git repository: genetic programming hyper-heuristics for evolving dispatching rules for job shop scheduling. My Git repository: meta-heuristic and hyper-heuristic algorithms for uncertain arc routing problem. My Git repository: genetic programming hyper-heuristic algorithms for stochastic orienteering problem. The ECJ Java library: https://cs.gmu.edu/~eclab/projects/ecj/. Highly recommeded if using GP. The gplearn Python library for GP: http://gplearn.readthedocs.io/en/stable. The DEAP Python library for GP: https://deap.readthedocs.io/en/master/. The HyFlex hyper-heuristic framework: http://www.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Section</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/custom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/custom/</guid>
      <description>This is an example of using the custom widget to create your own homepage section.
To remove this section, either delete content/home/teaching.md or edit the frontmatter of the file to deactivate the widget by setting active = false.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tags</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/tags/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/tags/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/people/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://meiyi1986.github.io/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>